An Inventory of the United States. Food Administration records XX066
Hoover Institution Archives
- Alphabetical file, 1901-1928, 1940-1942 (Folder 88-203,300-315, 420)
  - Reports, 1917-1940. (Folder 171)
    - Hearing before the Committee on Agriculture, 1919 (Folder 172: 2)
    - Annual Report for the Year 1918, Washington, 1919 (Folder 172: 3-5)
    - Introduction to Food Administration Report, by Herbert Hoover, 1920. (Folder 172: 6)
    - Official Statement of the U.S. Food Administration, nos. 1-18, Washington, June 1918 - September 1919 (Folder 172: 7-8)
    - Official Statement of the U.S. Wheat Director, nos. 1-11, New York, October 1919 - August 1920 (Folder 172: 9)
    - Provisional Statistical Statement of the Operations of the American Relief Administration and U.S. Food Administration Grain Corporation, January-February 1919, Paris (Folder 172: 10)
    - Final Report of the U.S. Food Administration, [various drafts], 1920, 1941 (Folder 172)
      - Volume I, circa 1920 (Folder 172: 11-14)
      - Volume II, circa 1920 (Folder 173: 1-8)
      - Manuscript, galley, lists, etc., by William C. Mullendore, 1941 (Folder 173: 9-14)
      - Manuscript, galley, lists, etc., by William C. Mullendore, 1941 (contd.) (Folder 174: 1-6)
      - Preface to a Report of the Food Administration, by Herbert Hoover, 1920 (Folder 174: 7)
      - Outline of History of the U.S. Food Administration, vol. I (Folder 174: 8-10)
  - Requa, Mark L.
    See 16-H; 20-H; 34-H
  - Resales, 1918 (Folder 174: 11)
  - Resume of resolutions, 1918 (Folder 174: 12)
  - Reuter, E. B.
    See 42-H
  - Rhondda, Lord.
    See Great Britain, Food Ministry
  - Rice.
    See Burma; 21-H; Grain, Rice, Siam
  - Richey, Lawrence.
    See 44-H Bean Investigation
  - Rickard, Edgar.
    See 10-H, Walcott
  - Roberts, G. H.
  - Roberts, T. J.
  - Robson, H. T.
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1917. (Folder 174: 13)
    See also International Health Board
  - Rogers, General H. L.
  - Rolph, George M.
    See 30-H; 48-H; Great Britain, USFA, Correspondence
  - Rope, 1918. (Folder 174: 14)
    See also Mexico, Exports and imports
  - Rose, Flora.
  - Roussy, M.
    See France, USFA
  - Rowe, L. S.
  - Roy, E. L.
    See 15-H; Great Britain, USFA, Correspondence
  - Rules and Reports Committee.
  - Rules and regulations in effect.
  - Rumania (Romania) (Folder 174: 15)
  - Rupple, H.
  - Russell, A. L.
    See 17-H; 46-H
  - Russia, 1916-1919. (Folder 174)
    See also Germany, Russian Relations; Sweden, Agreement with Russia
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 174: 16-17)
    - Agriculture, crops, and stocks, 1917-1919 (Folder 174: 18-19)
    - Agriculture, crops, and stocks, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 175: 1)
    - Archangelsk and Murmansk, 1918 (Folder 175: 2)
    - Bessarabia.
      See Rumania (Romania)
    - Exports and imports, 1917-1919 (Folder 175: 3)
    - Prices, 1917-1918 (Folder 175: 4)
    - Rations, 1917-1919. (Folder 175: 5)
      See also World Trade Board Research Bureau, Rationing, Northern Russia
    - Siberia, 1916-1919 (Folder 175)
    - General, 1916-1919 (Folder 175: 6)
    - Charles Holman reports, 1918-1919 (Folder 175: 7)
    - Ukraine, 1918-1919. (Folder 175: 8)
      See also Denmark, Germany, and Switzerland, Supplies from the Ukraine
  - Ryan, Charles B.
  - Rye.
    See Grain, Rye
  - S correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 175: 9-17)
  - S correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 176: 1-12)
  - Saccharine, 1912-1918. (Folder 176: 13)
    See also Exports, Saccharine
  - Saginaw Milling Co.
  - Sago, circa 1917 (Folder 176: 14)
  - Sales of Food and Clothing by Army Liquidation Commission, 1920 (Folder 176: 15)
  - Salmon.
    See Fish, Federal Trade Commission, Food Investigation, Report on canned foods, Canned salmon
  - Salt, 1917 (Folder 176: 16)
  - Saltpetre.
    See Potash, etc.
  - San Domingo.
  - Sands, Lewis E.
  - Sanford, Ethel H.
  - Scandinavia, General, 1911-1918 (Folder 177: 1-2)
  - Scandinavia, Post War Trade, 1918 (Folder 177: 3)
  - School Lunches.
    See M Correspondence, E. McClary; 5-H, Van Rensselaer
  - Scoofield, C. S.
  - Scott, John W.
    See War Industries Board, Textile Division
  - Scudder, S. J.
  - Secret Service.
    See Intelligence
  - Seeds, 1917-1918. (Folder 177: 4)
    See also Exports, Seeds
  - Seagall, J. B.
  - Senate Agricultural Committee.
  - Serbia, 1918-1919 (Folder 177: 5-7)
  - Sesame, 1919 (Folder 177: 8)
  - Shaw, A. W.
    See Council of National Defense; War Industries Board
  - Shaw, Anna Howard.
    See Council of National Defense. Woman's Committee
  - Shaw, Connor B.
    See 15-H, Correspondence with Arthur Meeker
  - Sheldon, L. P.
    See Great Britain, USFA, Correspondence; WYB, Foreign Agents, London
  - Sheppard, Morris.
  - Sherman, Edwin.
  - Shipping, 1915-1919.
    See also Allied Maritime Transport Council in International Food Control File, box 313
    - General, 1918 (Folder 177: 9)
    - Dutch, 1918. (Folder 177: 10)
      See also Neutrals
    - German, 1915-1916 (Folder 177: 11)
    - Ports, 1918 (Folder 177: 12)
    - Tonnage, 1917-1919 (Folder 177: 13)
    - U-Boat losses, 1918. (Folder 177: 14)
      See also Maxim Hudson
  - Shipping Board, 1917-1920 (Folder 177)
    - General, 1917-1920 (Folder 177: 15)
    - Edward N. Hurley, Chairman, 1917-1919 (Folder 177: 16-19)
    - Edward F. Carry, 1917-1918 (Folder 177: 20)
    - Japanese boats, 1918 (Folder 178: 1)
    - Shipping submarines, 1915-1918 (Folder 178: 2-4)
    - Northern relief ships, 1919 (Folder 178: 5)
  - Shipping Control Committee, Chairman Franklin, Philip Albright Small, 1918 (Folder 178: 6)
  - Shoes.
    See Leather and hides
  - Shouse, Jouett.
  - Siam, 1917-1918 (Folder 178: 7)
  - Silk industry of British India.
    See India
  - Silos, 1915-1918 (Folder 178: 8)
  - Silvercruys, Suzanne.
    See 6-H, Pennsylvania, Howard Heinz's addresses
  - Simpson, John L.
    See France, USFA, Correspondence; France [Food Reports for H. Hoover]; Great Britain, USFA, Correspondence
  - Sims, Admiral W. S. of Food Administration See Great Britain, USFA
  - Sisal, jute and binder twine.
    See Mexico, Exports and imports; 39-H; Prices, Sisal and Manila hemp
  - Smith, A. Burnett, 1918-1919 (Folder 178: 9)
  - Smith, Cecil.
  - Smith, Everett W.
    See 12-H; 45-H
  - Smith, H. Alexander.
    See 6-H; Great Britain, Food Ministry, Rations
  - Smith, J. Russell (Folder 178: 10)
  - Snyder, F. S.
    See 15-H; 22-H; 29-H
  - Soap, 1917 (Folder 178: 11)
  - Soda ash, caustic soda, bicarbonate of soda, 1918 (Folder 178: 12)
  - Sodium sulphate, 1918 (Folder 178: 13)
  - Sorghum.
    See Grain, Sorghum
  - Soups, 1918 (Folder 178: 14)
  - South America, 1918. (Folder 178: 15)
    See also Argentina; Brazil; Chile; World Trade Board, Research Bureau, Rationing, Latin America
  - Soya beans and soya bean products, 1917-1918 (Folder 178: 16)
  - Spain, 1916-1919. (Folder 178)
    See also World Trade Board, Foreign Agents, Madrid
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 178: 17)
    - Agreement with the United States, 1918 (Folder 178: 18)
    - Agriculture, crops, and stocks, 1916-1919 (Folder 178: 19)
    - Commercial Restrictions during the War, 2 December 1918 (Folder 178: 20)
    - Commission of Supplies, 1917-1919 (Folder 178: 21-22)
    - Exports and imports, 1917-1919 (Folder 178: 23)
    - German submarine base.
      See Germany, Submarine base in Spain
    - German ships, 1917-1918 (Folder 178: 24)
    - War supplies, 1917 (Folder 178: 25)
    - Washington Embassy, 1918 (Folder 178: 26)
  - Spamer, Carl O.
  - Speaking Division.
  - Speculation, 1917-1919 (Folder 179: 1)
  - Spens, C. E.
  - Spices, 1918 (Folder 179: 2)
  - Splint, Sarah Field.
  - Spreckels, Claus A.
    See 20-H
  - Spriggs, Edmund I.
  - Starch, 1917-1918 (Folder 179: 3)
  - State Department, 1917-1919
    - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 179: 4-5)
    - Division of Foreign Intelligence, Daily News Summary, 1918 (Folder 179: 6-8)
    - Personnel of foreign missions, 1917-1918 (Folder 179: 9)
    - Lansing, Robert, 1917-1919 (Folder 179: 10-15)
    - Phillips, William, 1918 (Folder 179: 16)
    - Polk, Frank Lyon, 1917-1919 (Folder 179: 17-20)
  - State fairs, 1917 (Folder 179: 21)
  - Statistical Clearing House.
    See Central Bureau of Planning and Statistics, Statistical Clearing House
  - Statistics, 1917-1918. (Folder 180: 1-5)
  - Sterling, John P.
  - Stewart, Stella.
    See 15-H; 21-H; 30-H; 35-H; 37-H; 42-H
  - Stewart, W. A. W.
    See World Trade Board, Foreign Agent
  - Strauss, Lewis L., correspondence, 1918. (Folder 180: 6-9)
    See also 1-H
  - Stream, John J.
  - Stuart, Governor Henry C.
    See Agricultural Advisory Committee
  - Sugar, 1915-1925.
    See also Cuba; 30-H; 46-H; 48-H
    - American Sugar Refining Company, 1916-1921
      - Reports, 1916-1921 (Folder 180: 10-13)
      - The American Sugar Bulletin, New York, 1918-1920 (Folder 180: 14-15)
      - The American Sugar Bulletin, New York, 1918-1920 (contd.) (Folder 181: 1)
    - Grain Corporation, correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 181: 2-5)
    - Sugar Equalization Board, correspondence, 1919-1921 (Folder 181: 6-9)
    - Sugar shortage investigation, 1917-1925 (Folder 181)
      - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 181: 10-12)
      - General, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 182: 1-8)
      - Spreckels, Babst, Woolwine, Bishop, Jones, Newberry, Whitley, Patterson, and Harms testimony, 1917 (Folder 182: 9-12)
      - Clippings, 1917-1925 (Folder 182: 13-16)
      - Clippings, 1917-1925 (contd.) (Folder 183: 1-3)
  - Sulgrave Institution, 1917-1918 (Folder 183: 4)
  - Sullivan, J.W.
  - Sulphur (Sulfur), sulphuric acid, sulphate, and pyrites, 1917-1918 (Folder 183: 5)
  - Sulzer, Hans.
  - Surface, Frank M.
    See 17-H; Wheat guaranty
  - Sweden, 1912-1919. (Folder 183)
    - General, 1917-1919 (Folder 183: 6-7)
    - Ekengren, W. A. F. Minister, 1917-1918 (Folder 183: 8)
    - Agreement with British, French and Italian governments, 1917 (Folder 183: 9)
    - Agreement with World Trade Board, 1917-1918 (Folder 183: 10-11)
    - Agriculture, crops, and stocks, 1917-1919 (Folder 183: 12)
    - A. R. Nordvall and H. de Lagercrantz delegates of the Royal Swedish Government, 1917-1918 (Folder 183: 13)
    - Exports and imports, 1912-1918 (Folder 183: 14-16)
    - Exports and imports, 1912-1918 (contd.) (Folder 184: 1)
    - Finance, 1918 (Folder 184: 2)
    - Fuel, 1917 (Folder 184: 3)
    - People's Household Commission, 1917-1918 (Folder 184)
      - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 184: 4)
      - Meat and Livestock, 1917-1918 (Folder 184: 5)
      - Prices, 1917-1919 (Folder 184: 6)
      - Rations, The Rationing System in Sweden, by Albert Halstead, 1918 (Folder 184: 7)
    - Shipping, 1918 (Folder 184: 8)
    - Trade with Germany, 1919 (Folder 184: 9)
  - Sweet, Lou D.
  - Swift, John W.
  - Swift, Louis F.
  - Swift and Company.
    See 15-H; Great Britain, USFA, Correspondence, Federal Trade Commission
  - Swine.
  - Swine Commission.
  - Switzerland, 1916-1919. (Folder 184)
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 184: 10)
    - Hans Sulzer, Minister, 1917-1918 (Folder 184: 11)
    - Agreements, 1917-1919 (Folder 184: 12-13)
    - Agriculture, crops, and stocks, 1917-1918 (Folder 184: 14)
    - American Expeditionary Forces, purchases, 1918 (Folder 184: 15)
    - Chemicals, 1918 (Folder 184: 16)
    - Commission Permanente Internationale des Contingents, 1918 (Folder 184: 17)
    - Exports and imports, 1916-1919. (Folder 184: 18-19)
      See also Switzerland, German Relations
    - Federal Food Office, 1917-1919 (Eidgenössisches Ernährungsamt, Office de l'Alimentation), 1917-1918 (Folder 184: 20)
      1917-1918
      - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 184: 20)
      - Bread and cereals, 1916-1918 (Folder 184: 21-22)
      - Bread and cereals, 1916-1918 (contd.) (Folder 185: 1)
      - Dairy products, 1918 (Folder 185: 2)
      - Meat and livestock, 1918 (Folder 185: 3)
      - Prices, 1918-1919 (Folder 185: 4)
      - Rations, 1917-1918 (Folder 185: 5)
      - Sugar, 1917-1918 (Folder 185: 6)
      - Forms, 1917-1918 (Folder 185: 7-8)
      - Fuel, 1918 (Folder 185: 9)
      - German relations, 1917-1918 (Folder 185: 10)
      - Reception of the Swiss Mission, by Archie Rice, 1918 (Folder 185: 11)
      - Shipping, 1917-1918 (Folder 185: 12)
      - Société Suisse de Surveillance Economique, 1918 (Folder 185: 13)
      - War Industrial Economy Department.
        See France, Ministry of Blockade and Liberal Regions, Committee on Restriction of Supplies and Commerce of the Enemy
      - War Trade Bureau, 1917-1919 (Folder 185: 14)
  - T correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 185: 15-19)
  - Taft, Robert A.
  - Tallents, S. G.
    See France, USFA; Great Britain, Food Ministry, Rations
  - Tallow.
    See Fats, Oils and oil seeds; 42-H
  - Tannic extract, 1917 (Folder 185: 20)
  - Tapioca.
    See Food substitutes
  - Tarbell, Ida M.
  - Tardieu, André.
    See France, French High Commission
  - Tariff Commission, Frank W. Taussig and William Kent, 1917-1919 (Folder 185: 21-22)
  - Tariff Commission, Inquiry into the Milling Division, 1918 (Folder 185: 23)
  - Tasmania, 1915-1917 (Folder 186: 1)
  - Why America Fights Germany, by John S. P. Tatlock, 1918 (Folder 186: 2)
  - Taussig, Frank W.
  - Taylor, Alonzo Englebert, Representative of the Secretary of Agriculture, 1916-1919.
    See also 11-H; 47-H; Germany, Grain, Wheat, Raw materials; World Trade Board
    - Correspondence A-Z, 1917-1919 (Folder 186: 3-9)
    - Recommendations for work, 1917 (Folder 186: 10)
    - Travelling expenses, 1917 (Folder 186: 11)
    - Conditions of Diet and Nutrition in the Interment Camp at Ruhleben, reports, 1916 (Folder 186: 12)
  - Taylor, F. G.
  - Telegraph Division.
  - Templin, Olin.
  - Textile industry, 1918 (Folder 186: 13)
  - Thackara, A. M.
    See France, Food reports
  - Third Liberty Loan.
  - Thomas, Dwight P.
  - Thompson, J. Walter, Advertising for the Food Administration.
    See 12-H, Advertising Division
  - Thorne, W. V. S.
  - Timber, 1917 (Folder 186: 14)
  - Tin plate, 1917-1918 (Folder 186: 15)
  - Tin, Regulation of Supplies of Tin Cans in World War I, 1916-1918, by J. D. Edwards and Stella Stewart, 1941 (Folder 186: 16)
  - Tobago.
  - Tobacco, 1917-1918 (Folder 186: 17)
  - Toluol, 1917-1918 (Folder 186: 18)
  - Tomatoes.
    See Vegetables, Tomatoes
  - Tonnage.
    See Shipping, Tonnage
  - Topeka Flour Mills.
  - Tractors, correspondence, 1917-1918
    - A-F, 1917-1918 (Folder 186: 19-22)
    - G-Y, 1917-1918 (Folder 187: 1-8)
    - French High Commission, 1917-1918 (Folder 187: 9)
    - Morgenthau, Henry (Jr. and Sr.), 1917-1918 (Folder 187: 10)
    - Tractor Advisory Committee, 1918 (Folder 187: 11)
  - Trade resumption.
    See Post War Trade and Reconstruction
  - Transportation.
    See 31-H; 36-H
  - Treasury Department, 1917-1919 (Folder 187)
    - General, 1917-1919 (Folder 187: 12)
    - William G. McAdoo, Secretary, 1917-1918 (Folder 188: 1-3)
    - Carter Glass, Secretary, 1917-1919 (Folder 188: 4)
    - Oscar T. Crosby, Acting Secretary, 1917-1918. (Folder 188: 5)
      See also Great Britain, USFA, correspondence
    - Assisting secretaries, 1917-1919 (Folder 188)
      - L. S. Rowe, 1918 (Folder 188: 6)
      - R. C. Leffingwell, 1917-1919 (Folder 188: 7-8)
      - Albert Rathbone, 1918-1919 (Folder 188: 9-10)
      - Norman H. Davis, 1918 (Folder 188: 11)
      - R. C. Cooksey, 1917-1918 (Folder 188: 12)
    - W. W. Warwick, Controller of the Treasury, 1917-1919 (Folder 188: 13)
    - E. D. Hearne, Auditor, 1918 (Folder 188: 14)
    - John Skelton Williams, Comptroller of the Currency, 1918 (Folder 188: 15)
    - Daniel C. Roper, Commissioner of Internal Revenue, 1917-1918 (Folder 188: 16)
    - W. H. Moran, Secret Service, 1919 (Folder 188: 17)
    - Herbert Quick, Federal Farm Loan Bureau, 1917-1918 (Folder 188: 18)
    - War Risk Insurance Bureau, 1917-1918 (Folder 188: 19)
    - National War-Savings Committee, 1917 (Folder 188: 20)
  - Trinidad.
  - Tungsten, 1917 (Folder 188: 21)
  - Turkey, 1918 (Folder 188: 22)
  - Turkey for Thanksgiving, 1918 (Folder 188: 23)
  - U Correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 188: 24)
  - Ukraine.
    See Russia, Ukraine
  - United States Army, 1918-1919
    1939
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 189: 1-2)
    - General Staff, Statistics Branch, Food Situation for 1918, 1 May 1918 (Folder 189: 3-4)
  - United States Navy, 1917-1918 (Folder 189: 5)
  - Uruguay, 1917-1919 (Folder 189: 6)
  - V Correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 189: 7-9)
  - Van Hise, Charles R.
  - Van Rensselaer, Martha.
  - Van Sicklen, F. W.
  - Van Winkle, Mrs. Mina C.
  - Veblen, Thorstein, 1918 (Folder 189: 10)
  - Vegetables, 1917-1919 (Folder 189)
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 189: 11)
    - Beans and peas, 1917-1918 (Folder 189: 12-13)
    - Cabbage, 1918 (Folder 189: 14)
    - Onions, 1917-1918 (Folder 189: 15)
    - Potatoes, 1917-1919 (Folder 189: 16)
    - Potatoes, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 190: 1)
    - Tomatoes, 1918 (Folder 190: 2)
  - Venezuela, 1918 (Folder 190: 3)
  - Vilgrain J. E.
    See France, Food Administration reports, R-17; France, Food Ministry
  - Vital Statistics, 1917-1918. (Folder 190: 4)
    See also Germany and Great Britain, Vital statistics
  - Vivisection, 1917 (Folder 190: 5)
  - Vories, Harry F. (Folder 190)
    See Bread and baking; 21-H
  - W Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 190: 6-15)
  - W Correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 191: 1-5)
  - Walcott, Frederic Collin, Correspondence re Romance of the Food Administration, 1919, 1926, 1928. (Folder 191: 6-7)
    See also 9-H, Richard Carr and Walcott
  - Wallace, Henry E., 1917-1918 (Folder 191: 8)
  - Walters, B. R.
  - War Commissions, Allied and Neutral, list of personnel, circa 1918 (Folder 191: 9)
  - War cost, 1917-1918 (Folder 191: 10)
    1938
  - War Department, 1917-1919 (Folder 190)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 191: 11-13)
    - Newton D. Baker, Secretary, 1917-1919 (Folder 191: 14-15)
    - Major General Enoch H. Crowder, Provost Marshal General, 1918-1919 (Folder 191: 16)
    - General R. E. Wood, 1918 (Folder 192: 1)
    - Surgeon General's Office, Physical Examination of the First Million Draft Recruits; Methods and Results, 1919 (Folder 192: 2)
  - War Finance Corporation, 1918 (Folder 192: 3)
  - War Gardens, National War Garden Commission, 1918 (Folder 192: 4-5)
  - War Industries Board, 1917-1919, 1921, 1941 (Folder 192)
    - General, 1971-1918 (Folder 192: 6-8)
    - Bernard M. Baruch, Chairman, 1917, 1921 (Folder 192: 9)
    - Chemical Division, 1918 (Folder 192: 10)
    - Conservation Division, 1918 (Folder 192: 11)
    - Directory, 1918 (Folder 192: 12)
    - Fire Prevention Section, 1918 (Folder 193: 13)
    - Planning and Statistics Division, 1918 (Folder 192)
      - Bulletin of Monthly Prices during the War, no. 1, 1918 (Folder 192: 14)
      - Bulletin of Monthly Prices during the War, nos. 2-3, 1918 (Folder 193: 1-2)
      - Complete List of Wholesale Prices, 1918 (Folder 193: 3)
      - Price Fixing Bulletin; Market Prices of Commodities under Control, nos. 1-15, 1918 (Folder 193: 4-10)
      - A Comparison of Prices during the Civil War and Present War, 1918 (Folder 193: 11)
      - Weekly Bulletin on Raw Materials, 1918 (Folder 194: 1-4)
      - Commodity Bulletin; Weekly Report, 1918 (Folder 194: 5-9)
      - The Food Situation; A Monthly Study as of November 1, 1918 (Folder 194: 10)
    - Price Fixing Committee, Robert S. Brookings, Chairman, 1917-1918 (Folder 195: 1)
    - Priorities Division, Edwin B. Parker, R. S. Lovett, 1917-1918 (Folder 195: 2-3)
    - Pulp and Paper Section, Thomas E. Donnelley, 1918 (Folder 195: 4)
    - Requirements Division, Alexander Legge, 1917-1918 (Folder 195: 5)
    - Steel Division, J. Leonard Replogle, Director, 1917-1918 (Folder 195: 6)
    - Textile Division, John W. Scott, 1918 (Folder 195: 7)
    - Preliminary Inventory of the War Industries Board Records, The National Archives, 1941 (Folder 195: 8)
  - War legislation, 1917-1918 (Folder 195: 9-13)
  - War prohibition, 1916-1918 (Folder 195: 14)
  - War Trade Board (WTB), 1917-1920. (Folder 195)
    See also 11-H, box 419; Exports; Imports
    - General, 1918-1919 (Folder 195: 15-16)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 196: 1-3)
    - Vance C. McCormick, Chairman, 1917-1918 (Folder 196: 4-5)
    - John Beaver White, Experts Administrative Board, 1917-1918 (Folder 196: 6-8)
    - Theodore Frothingham, Assistant to J. B. White, 1917-1918 (Folder 196: 9)
    - W. K. Macy, Department of Exports and Imports, 1917-1918 (Folder 196: 10-15)
    - Clarence M. Woolley, Representative of the Secretary Of Commerce, 1918-1919 (Folder 197: 1)
    - Alonzo E. Taylor, Representative of the Secretary of Agriculture, 1917-1918 (Folder 197: 2-4)
    - Sidney A. Mitchell, 1918 (Folder 197: 5)
    - Legation of the USA, Berne, Switzerland, 1918 (Folder 197: 6)
    - Branches and Customs Bureau, 1918 (Folder 197: 7)
    - Cable censorship memorandum, 1917 (Folder 197)
    - Cables, 1918 (Folder 197: 8-12)
    - Chemical Advisory Committee, 1917-1918 (Folder 197: 13)
    - Policy and Achievement of the War Trade Board, report by S. B. Conger, 8 December 1918 (Folder 197: 14)
    - Contraband Committee, 1918 (Folder 197: 15)
    - Daily Digest of News and Comments, (incomplete), 18 December 1917 - 15 January 1919 (Folder 197: 16)
    - Daily Record (nos. 364, 386, 394, 399), 30 November 1918 - 13 January 1919 (Folder 197: 17)
    - Directory, September 1918 (Folder 197: 18)
    - Enemy Trade Bureau, 1917-1919 (Folder 197: 19-21)
    - Exports Bureau, 1917-1918 (Folder 198: 1-3)
    - Foreign Agents and Reports Bureau, 1918 (Folder 198)
      - General, 1918 (Folder 198: 4)
      - Berne (Bern), Ellis Loring Dresel, 1918 (Folder 198: 5)
      - London, L. P. Sheldon, 1918. (Folder 198: 6)
        See also Great Britain, Food Administration, Correspondence
      - Madrid, W. A. Chadbourne, 1918 (Folder 198: 7)
      - Paris, George McFadden, 1918 (Folder 198: 8)
      - Rome, W. A. W. Stewart, 1918 (Folder 198: 9)
      - Stockholm, William H. Owen, 1918 (Folder 198: 10)
    - Forms, 1918 (Folder 198: 11)
    - Government Control over Prices, Price Bulletin no. 3, 1918.
    - Imports Bureau, 1918-1919 (Folder 198: 12)
    - Information Division, 1918 (Folder 198: 13)
    - Intelligence, 1917-1918 (Folder 198: 14)
    - Journals, nos. 1-10, 12-17, 19, 1917-1919 (Folder 198: 15-17)
    - Licenses requested.
      See Alonzo E. Taylor, box 196
    - Minutes (extracts), 12 February - 10 December 1918 (Folder 198: 18)
    - Press releases, nos. 1-15, 17-79, December 1918 - February 1919 (Folder 198: 19-20)
    - Press Summary "For Mr. McCormick," (incomplete), 17 June - 6 September 1918 (Folder 199: 1)
    - Regulations, nos. 1-541 (incomplete), 1917-1919 (Folder 199: 2-9)
    - Bunker fuel, port, sea, and ship's stores and supplies regulations, 1918 (Folder 199: 10)
    - Compiled Statement of Import Restrictions and Relaxations Made up to and Including January 6, 1919 (Folder 199: 11)
    - Rules and Regulations, no. 2, Manual for Shippers, 1918 (Folder 199: 12)
    - Rules and Regulations Governing the Exports of Foodstuffs and Feeding stuffs, 1918 (Folder 199: 13)
    - Reports, 1917, 1920 (Folder 199: 14)
    - Research Bureau, 1917-1919. (Folder 200)
      See also Paper and pulp industry
      - General, 1917-1919 (Folder 200: 1)
      - Country studies, Netherlands, Spain, Norway, and Switzerland, 1918 (Folder 200: 2)
      - Cross Shipments-United Kingdom to the Americas, and United States to Europe, 1918 (Folder 200: 3)
      - List of Data Available in the Files of the Bureau of Research, War Trade Board, 1918-1919 (Folder 200: 4-7)
      - Rationing, Northern Russia, Latin America, 1918 (Folder 200: 8-9)
      - Russian Bureau, Inc., 1918 (Folder 200: 10)
      - Tabulations and Statistics Bureau, 1917 (Folder 200: 11)